<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Timemanagement</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="links">Links</string>
    <string name="add_task">Add Task</string>
    <string name="TMQ">TMQ</string>
    <string name="new_task">New task</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="Start_questionnaire">Start questionnaire</string>

    <string name="TMQ_info">The time-management questionnaire included 35 items, each answered on a 5-point scale consisting of the responses always, frequently, sometimes, infrequently, and never).
        In scoring, 5 points were assigned to the response at the end of the scale that we defined a priori as the "good" practice and 1 point was assigned to the response at the other end of the scale, with intermediate values given for the other responses.
        Higher values on the scale correspond to better timemanagement practices.</string>
    <string name="final_score">Final score</string>
    <string name="total_score">Total score:</string>
    <string name="short_range_planning_score">Short-Range Planning score:</string>
    <string name="time_attitudes_score">Time Attitudes score:</string>
    <string name="long_range_planning_score">Long-Range Planning score:</string>

    <string name="quest_1">Do you make a list of the things you have to do each day?</string>
    <string name="quest_2">Do you plan your day before you start it?</string>
    <string name="quest_3">Do you make a schedule of the activities you have to do on work days?</string>
    <string name="quest_4">Do you write a set of goals for yourself for each day?</string>
    <string name="quest_5">Do you spend time each day planning?</string>
    <string name="quest_6">Do you have a clear idea of what you want to accomplish during the next week?</string>
    <string name="quest_7">Do you set and honor priorities?</string>
    <string name="quest_8_a">Do you often find yourself doing things which interfere with your schoolwork simply because you hate to say "No" to people?</string>
    <string name="quest_9">Do you feel you are in charge of your own time, by and large?</string>
    <string name="quest_10_a">On an average class day do you spend more time with personal grooming than doing schoolwork?</string>
    <string name="quest_11_a">Do you believe that there is room for improvement in the way you manage your time?</string>
    <string name="quest_12">Do you make constructive use of your time?</string>
    <string name="quest_13_a">Do you continue unprofitable routines or activities?</string>
    <string name="quest_14">Do you usually keep you desk clear of everything other than what you are currently working on?</string>
    <string name="quest_15">Do you have a set of goals for the entire quarter?</string>
    <string name="quest_16_a">The night before a major assignment is due, are you usually still working on it?</string>
    <string name="quest_17">When you have several things to do, do you think it is best to do a little bit of work on each one?</string>
    <string name="quest_18">Do you regularly review your class notes, even when a test is not imminent?</string>

    <string-array name="task_arts_array">
        <item>All tasks</item>
        <item>Completed tasks</item>
        <item>Upcoming tasks</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
